http://www.naturecare.com.au/media-and-events/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Nature Care respects your privacy:
Nature Care Pty Ltd (Nature Care) has created this Privacy Policy and Collection Statement (Policy) in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy.
We will update this policy as required. If it is changed, we will post details of the changes on our web site www.naturecare.com.au so that you are always aware of the sort of information we collect from you, how we may use that information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information.
If we are required by law at any time to release information about you, we must cooperate fully.
What information do we collect and how do we collect personal information from you?
If you subscribe to our (monthly) newsletter we will ask you to complete a form and provide us with your email address, your name and address.
When you visit our web site, our server logs your IP address (a number that is unique to the machine through which you are connected to the Internet), the type of browser and operating system you are using and the date and time of your visit.
We also use cookies to assign identification to your computer. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your web browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow our web site to store and reference certain types of information while you are visiting a site. Our cookies contain no personal or financial information. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, although your browser preferences may be changed to prevent this if you wish.
What happens if you do not provide the information?
We will be unable to send you our newsletter or other information such as changes to our web site if you do not provide us with your email address.
If you change your browser preferences to prevent use of our cookies, we will not be able to store and reference any of the non personal information designed to be obtained by the cookie. However, your ability to enter and view our web site will be unaffected.
Why do we collect personal information from you and how do we use that information?
We collect information from you so that we can email our newsletter to you. This is the only use we make of the information. We will not sell, rent, trade or otherwise supply to any third party any personal information obtained from you without your consent.
How will we keep your personal information secure?
We have security measures designed to protect against the loss, misuse and/or alteration of any personal information supplied by you to us.
Correcting and updating your profile?
You may gain access to information that we have collected from you by contacting us. We will not charge you for responding to such a request (unless we incur costs in providing the information).
Nature Care College Privacy Policy & Procedures
we are social
Nature Care College extends its reach and communication with our current students, alumni, partners and general public through social media platforms. Make sure you stay in touch for the latest news and events regarding open days, seminars, treatments and all types of courses from one day workshops to more advanced programmes.
Courses
On-line Learning Courses Anatomy & Chemistry Aromatherapy Astrology Ayurvedic Health Coaching & Wellbeing
Energetic Health Gratitude Training Practices
Holistic Nutrition Meditation Facilitation Naturopathic Health & Wellness Reiki Short Courses Tarot & Numerology Western Herbal Medicine
enrolment
How to Enrol - New Students
Enrolment Forms Payment Options Recognition of Prior Learning International Students
Testimonials
media & events
College News Promotions Events Disclaimer Privacy Policy Join Mailing List
Timetables Student Forms Student Handbooks Managing Your Studies
Nature Care College | P: 02 8423 8333 | E: info@naturecare.com.au
| Login |
Disclaimer | Privacy Policy
| Site Map
